# **Jeffrey Jarvis**

jeffrey.jarvis32@gmail.com • M: 678.602.2673 • LinkedIn

#### MISSION STATEMENT

With over seven years of experience working complex sales cycles with C-level executives, I've grown a passion for driving revenue in exciting growth environments. Currently, I'm exploring continued education to more effectively engage with product teams and am aspiring to bridge the gap between product and sales.

\_\_\_\_\_

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GreenSky Inc. Atlanta, GA

## **Enterprise Client Growth Manager**

Dec 2019 – Present

- Consistently achieving 110% of monthly quotas
- Strategizing with owners, sales managers, and sales teams to drive growth for their businesses
- Managing sales training seminars for internal and external clients to maximize field utilization, and increase closing rates and average contract value
- Leading existing customer data deep dives to refine custom sales programs for their unique markets

## **Onboarding Specialist – Mid Market**

June 2018 – Dec 2019

- Awarded 2019 "Team MVP of the Year" for leading the team in new client activations
- Educated incoming customers about GreenSky software to encourage usage and excitement
- Pitched tailored sales programs and led trainings for net new clients to drive engagement

Izenda Inc. Atlanta, GA

**Account Executive** 

June 2017 – June 2018

- Achieved quarterly quotas goals in the first six months
- Navigated highly technical sales cycles working with all aspects of prospecting accounts including executive management, developer teams, and product teams
- Led sales analysis and forecasting for hundreds of accounts and prospects, reducing sales cycle
- Worked directly with Izenda CEO, implementing strategies designed to boost sales acumen and speed to sale

Gartner Inc. Fort Myers, FL
Account Manager Jan 2016 – May 2017

- Enhanced and managed a book of business increasing revenue by 50% in a year and saved \$250,000 of risky renewals
- Prospected new customers through cold calling, email communications, social media networking, and in-person meetings, achieving 156% of quota in nine months
- Developed relationships with current clients, drove added ROI via ongoing consultative engagements and provided strategic direction and innovative insights resulting in an average of 25% YoY revenue growth

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML CSS JavaScript Bootstrap JQuery Node.js

## **EDUCATION**

Kennesaw State University

Bachelor of Business Administration, Professional Sales

Kennesaw, GA

Dec 2015

Georgia Institute of Technology

Certification of Software Development

Atlanta, GA

June 2022